How was your day today ?
How was it ?
Well then ,
shall we talk ?
First , tell me about yourself .
Who do you think you are ?
Do you know who this is ?
Don 't know ?
It 's your family .
Want to see it again ?
Fine then .
Can you tell me
about that day ?
About what happened ?
You should be able to remember it clearly .
It 's okay .
Now ...
tell me what happened .
Aren 't you getting out ?
Su-yeon .
Su-yeon !
It 's so pretty .
Give me your hand .
The other one .
Why ?
Su-mi !
Welcome home !
It 's been such a long time .
You 've changed so much , Su-yeon .
You 've gotten prettier ...
But you two really disappointed me .
I waited all day for you two ,
cooking and cleaning the house ,
and you don 't even come to say hi first ?
What did you do ?
Were you at the wharf ?
You should 've changed first before you went outside .
Anyway ,
welcome back home .
Is something wrong ?
I see you 've gotten better .
I 'm so glad you feel better now .
You 're taking after your mom .
You 're feeling a lot better too , right ?
Right . I bet you 're both tired .
Get some rest and come down for dinner .
I 'm preparing a special dinner .
But you should give me some time .
There 's a lot to prepare .
We just got back .
Things don 't look so good right now .
It wouldn 't help much if you came .
Yeah , I know .
Let 's talk later . I should go .
So you 're doing okay , right ?
Did I tell you ?
Sun-kyu and his wife are coming over .
lt 'll be alright . I 'll take care of it .
Okay , bye .
Oh right !
I invited Sun-kyu and his wife over for dinner this weekend .
Really ?
It 'll be nice for them to see the girls after so long .
And to catch up on things .
That was delicious .
Sorry , I have things to tend to .
You must be tired , so clean it up tomorrow .
Did you prepare your father 's undergarments ?
Thanks , but that 's my job .
Cleaning my room is my job , too .
Why 'd you touch my stuff ?
That 's how it was before .
So all of the same clothes were hanging there before ?
I 'm not having dinner with him .
What ?
I said I 'm not having dinner with that guy .
He 's not some guy . He 's your uncle .
It 's the first day so let 's give it a rest .
And you ?
Yes ?
Aren 't you going to follow her ?
You 're supposed to follow your sister .
What did that woman tell you ?
If she ever gets on your case then tell me .
And don 't ignore it like before .
Okay ?
Good night .
What 's wrong ?
Did you have a bad dream ?
Was it the closet ?
Then what 's wrong ?
I keep hearing strange noises outside .
It 's because you 've been away too long .
It 's okay .
Let 's sleep .
Somebody
came into my room .
He 's asleep .
I know .
Then why are you trying to wake him ?
Says who ?
You were trying to wake him just now .
Have something to tell him ?
It 's none of your business .
All I 'm saying is he 's fast asleep .
Don 't wake him up . Don 't you understand me ?
I just came down for water .
He 's asleep , so be quiet .
Did you go to my room ?
Yes .
Who was it ?
That woman .
Stepmom ?
Yeah .
It 's strange .
What is ?
That woman is strange .
And so is this house .
Are you scared ?
Everything 's alright .
I 'm here .
Come here . Let 's sleep .
I 'll always be with you .
Su-yeon . Go away .
Are you awake ?
Yes .
Can I come in ?
No .
Come down and eat .
What are you doing ?
Are you having your period ?
No , Su-yeon is ...
Su-yeon ?
That 's so funny .
How could we both get our periods on the same date ?
Su-mi ...
It 's okay , come down .
That 's mom 's favorite , huh ?
Do it like this .
Shall we kill them ?
Let 's set them free .
She 'll have a cow if we mess with her precious .
I 'd hate to see that .
Su-mi .
What are you doing out in the cold ?
Are you alright ?
Why ?
You don 't look so good .
Are you feeling sick ?
No , I 'm okay .
Tell me , what 's wrong ?
I said I 'm okay .
Just get rid of Su-yeon 's closet .
Su-mi ,
we agreed not to talk about that closet .
You promised , right ?
Su-mi .
I know you 're very angry with me .
And I know I 'm a bad father .
You 're not even a bad father .
It 's cold , so let 's go inside .
I will .
What are you doing ?
You scared me .
When did you come in ?
Did you go to the warehouse ?
Yeah .
Su-yeon , look at this .
Tada !
Wow .
Pretty , huh ?
Cool .
Is it mom 's ?
Yup , and ...
There 's more .
It 's mom !
Taritakoom , taritakoom .
What does that mean ?
It 's a spell to call mom .
Who told you that ?
Mom did .
What ?
Can I take this ?
Huh ? Sure ...
This ...
and this .
Wait !
What is this ?
Who did this to you ?
Tell me , who did this ?
It 's okay , tell me .
She did this , right ?
She did this , didn 't she ?
Su-yeon , what 's wrong with you ?
I told you to tell me everything !
She did this , right ?
She did this , huh ?
Did she do this ?
Tell me ! Tell me ! Tell me ! Tell me !
What ?
How can you be so cruel ?
It 's retribution .
If you disobey , you need to be punished .
Does dad know what you did ?
Think your father can solve everything ?
Then go get him .
Want me to do it ?
Sit down !
Where are your manners ?
Were you like this to your mom , too ?
Don 't bring up my mom !
Listen carefully . I 'm your mother , got it ?
As much as you hate it .
I 'm the only one in this world you can call mother , got it ?
Crying over your mom 's photos won 't change anything .
Hard to handle ?
That 's too bad .
But that 's how the world is .
The world isn 't as sweet as you picture it .
Sometimes you have to bear the worst and live on .
Like the way I 'm bearing you two !
Tough , isn 't it ?
I have bore you two brats
from the moment I came to this house .
I have never met such ill-mannered menaces like you two .
What ?
Why the hell did you even come here ?
I can 't believe you said that to me again .
I see ,
you must be still sick .
Don 't touch me .
Let go !
What 's wrong with you ?
Are you that clueless ?
Don 't touch me with those filthy hands !
Su-mi , listen to me .
I don 't want to hear it . You 're the same .
That 's not true . You 've misunderstood .
You 're not even accepting all this .
Why is it always me ?
Why are you asking only me to understand ?
Are you really clueless ?
Yeah .
Maybe I don 't know .
I don 't have all the answers .
I don 't know , so tell me and let it off your chest .
Tell me !
Will it change anything ?
Will it ?
Su-mi .
Don 't do this .
Please don 't .
You 'll get sick again .
What ?
Fine .
From now on anything that happens here ,
all the filthy things you brought here ,
be responsible for it all .
I have nothing more to say , so answer the phone .
Do you remember ?
My memory 's a bit blurry but I think it did happen .
When was it ?
Hey , remember this ?
You jumped into the river
to catch some fish .
Then you started to drown ,
and everyone had a fit .
There was another funny story .
What was it ? Oh yeah , I remember .
Remember that crazy guy ?
The funny thing is is that he was always normal ,
but whenever it rained he went nuts .
While plowing the field
he 'd strip off his clothes when it rained ,
and run out into the highway .
The funniest time was
when it rained off and on .
So he 'd put on and take off his clothes , again and again .
Then he got sick of it and just went into his house .
Everyone in the neighborhood laughed so much back then .
But when ...
But when he was little , he saw him doing that once .
He saw him doing that once and then he ran together
with that crazy guy .
Our mom saw that and she almost passed out .
Do you remember ?
You remember , right ?
Say something .
Don 't you remember ?
You remember , right ?
No .
I don 't remember .
What ?
I said I don 't remember .
Why don 't you remember ?
Are you crazy ?
Mi-hee !
Wait , hold on to her .
What 's wrong ?
Wake up !
Bring some water .
Are you alright , Mi-hee ?
Water , water .
I 'm sorry , it 's all my fault .
Mi-hee !
It 's okay .
It 's alright , Mi-hee .
It 's alright .
I 'm sorry .
I didn 't want to come , but your father begged me to ,
so I had no choice .
Honey .
Yes ?
I saw something strange in that house .
What did you see ?
There was a girl under the sink .
Just go in .
Can 't you just stay here ?
Why ?
It 's strange .
What 's strange ?
After the girls came down
weird things have been happening in this house .
Don 't say stupid things .
Didn 't you see it ?
You 're just having a hard time adjusting .
You 'll get better if you rest .
No .
There is
something in this house .
I 'll look around , so lie down .
Open the door !
Open it !
Open the god damn door !
I 'll show you .
Get up !
Get off the bed .
Get off now !
I said now !
Come here , right now !
You pest ...
Talk !
A person can 't get any rest around this household .
Tell me . Who did it ?
Who did it ?
Who ? Better tell me the truth .
Who did it !
Was it Su-mi ?
You two need to learn a lesson !
Was it your sister ?
So do you feel better looking at your dead mom 's things ?
Feel happy after seeing the photos ?
Say that you 're sorry .
Until you do , don 't even think about coming out .
There 's no use in crying .
Say that you 're sorry and beg for forgiveness !
I 'm sorry .
What ?
Say it right .
I 'm sorry .
I 'll ask you once more .
You 're admitting that you 're sorry , right ?
Stop crying .
I don 't want to hear it , so stop it now !
Are you ...
Are you mad ?
Is that why you 're crying ?
Fine , let 's see how long you hold up .
This will put some sense into you two .
Su-yeon .
Su-yeon , I 'm sorry .
I didn 't hear you .
I 'm sorry , Su-yeon .
I 'm sorry .
This won 't happen again .
I promise .
Don 't cry , it 's okay .
Tell me .
What ?
Why the hell are you doing this ?
Tell me why you 've acted
so weird since you got here .
You really don 't know ?
Don 't know what ? What is it ?
I 'm talking about what that woman is doing to us !
So tell me what has she done ?
She keeps harassing Su-yeon .
What ?
Didn 't you hear me ?
I said she keeps harassing Su-yeon !
She 's vicious , evil ,
and always locks Su-yeon up in the closet !
Su-mi , please stop it .
Stop what ?
You know that Su-yeon is scared of her .
Su-yeon , you tell dad .
Stop crying and tell him now .
Tell him !
Please stop it !
Su-yeon ... is dead .
What ?
No ...
Su-yeon is dead .
So pull yourself together .
How long will you keep this up ?
It 's not true , Su-yeon .
Su-yeon ...
Su-yeon ... No ... No ...
Come down tomorrow , I can 't do it alone .
Hmm ...
She 's getting worse .
I 'll pick you up . Call me when you get here .
Su-mi , I 'm going out for a bit . I 'll be back by evening . Make sure to lock the door .
Su-yeon !
Su-mi !
I am fed up with your family .
How did we ...
How did we come to this ?
Don 't you get it yet ?
Remember what I told you before ?
Remember when I said you 'll regret it some day ?
You ...
Know what 's really scary ?
You want
to forget something .
Totally wipe it off of your mind .
But you never can .
It can 't go away , you see .
And ...
And it follows you around
like a ghost .
Help me .
Sure ,
I 'll help you .
Let 's end it here .
Su-mi !
Where 's Su-mi ?
Where ?
Please stop it .
I 'm sick of it now .
Take this , you 'll feel much better .
Su-mi !
Don 't you get it yet ?
You 're just having a hard time adjusting .
You must be still sick .
You promised not to bring up that closet .
How could we both get our periods on the same date ?
Su-yeon is dead !
No , I don 't remember !
Su-mi , are you okay ?
It 's all over now .
You 'll feel better here .
Get some rest .
I 'll come and visit often .
Take care of yourself .
Bye .
Su-mi , what 's wrong ?
Let go .
Let go , Su-mi .
Please stop it and let go .
No , I 'll get it .
Let me take one .
Mom ...
Su-yeon !
Mom ?
Mom , mom !
Mom ! Mom , mom , mom !
Mom !
Didn 't you hear something ?
Why 'd you come up here ?
Dad 's not here .
What do you mean by that ?
Now you 're trying to act like mom .
Do me a favor .
Stay out of our lives .
Can you get out of the way ?
I have to go .
You ...
You might regret this moment .
Keep that in mind !
What can be worse than standing here with you ?
When you 're here I wanna be as far away from you as I can .
Understand ?
Su-mi !
Help me ... Su-mi ...
Su-mi ... Su-mi ...
Su-mi ...